kollystills.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy of kollystills.com

We collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, we collect and store certain information automatically. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website.

**What We Collect and Store Automatically:**

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

•The Internet domain (for example, “kollystills.com” if you use a private Internet access account, and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;

•The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;

•The date and time you access our site;

•The pages you visit; and

•If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website. We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

•We use outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/ or web beacons and are collected by the ad companies. We do not have access to this collected information. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**If You Send Us E-mail:  ** You may choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. We do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations.

**Links to Other Sites:** Our website has many links to other websites. When you link to another website, you are no longer on our website and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

Contact Us: [info@kollystills.com](mailto:info@kollystills.com)
